const quizQuestions = [
  {
    question: "1. What is the chemical symbol for water?",
    options: ["H2O", "CO2", "O2", "N2"],
    correctAnswer: "H2O",
  },
  {
    question: "2. Which planet is known as the 'Red Planet'?",
    options: ["Earth", "Mars", "Venus", "Jupiter"],
    correctAnswer: "Mars",
  },
  {
    question: "3. What is the powerhouse of the cell?",
    options: [
      "Nucleus",
      "Mitochondria",
      "Endoplasmic Reticulum",
      "Golgi Apparatus",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Mitochondria",
  },
  {
    question: "4. Who developed the theory of general relativity?",
    options: [
      "Isaac Newton",
      "Galileo Galilei",
      "Albert Einstein",
      "Stephen Hawking",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Albert Einstein",
  },
  {
    question: "5. What is the smallest unit of matter?",
    options: ["Atom", "Molecule", "Cell", "Electron"],
    correctAnswer: "Atom",
  },
  {
    question: "6. What is the largest planet in our solar system?",
    options: ["Earth", "Jupiter", "Saturn", "Neptune"],
    correctAnswer: "Jupiter",
  },
  {
    question: "7. Which gas do plants absorb from the atmosphere?",
    options: ["Oxygen", "Carbon Dioxide", "Nitrogen", "Hydrogen"],
    correctAnswer: "Carbon Dioxide",
  },
  {
    question: "8. What is the Earth's primary source of energy?",
    options: ["Wind", "Solar", "Fossil Fuels", "Nuclear"],
    correctAnswer: "Solar",
  },
  {
    question: "9. Which scientist developed the three laws of motion?",
    options: [
      "Isaac Newton",
      "Albert Einstein",
      "Galileo Galilei",
      "Niels Bohr",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Isaac Newton",
  },
  {
    question: "10. What is the chemical symbol for gold?",
    options: ["Au", "Ag", "Fe", "Cu"],
    correctAnswer: "Au",
  },
  {
    question: "11. Which gas is responsible for the greenhouse effect?",
    options: ["Oxygen", "Carbon Dioxide", "Methane", "Nitrous Oxide"],
    correctAnswer: "Carbon Dioxide",
  },
  {
    question: "12. What is the speed of light?",
    options: ["300,000 km/s", "150,000 km/s", "500,000 km/s", "1,000,000 km/s"],
    correctAnswer: "300,000 km/s",
  },
  {
    question: "13. What is the largest organ in the human body?",
    options: ["Heart", "Liver", "Skin", "Brain"],
    correctAnswer: "Skin",
  },
  {
    question: "14. Which element has the chemical symbol 'O'?",
    options: ["Osmium", "Oxygen", "Oganesson", "Olivine"],
    correctAnswer: "Oxygen",
  },
  {
    question: "15. What is the main function of the red blood cells?",
    options: [
      "Transporting Oxygen",
      "Fighting Infections",
      "Producing Insulin",
      "Digesting Food",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Transporting Oxygen",
  },
];
